This is the most shocking murder
in more than twenty years.
Dr.Chonlathorn's killer gene theory is about to be disproved.
The victim died from being bitten
by red ants that bit his internal organs.
Then we have to start investigating these yarns.
Do you have this yarn?
Morse code.
Sky is an autistic teenager.
Where did it go? There must be four sheets in total.
3/10 is missing.
0001/1010
If we want to investigate the mother,
we have to approach her daughter.
Because kids with autism
-don't lie.
-Hello, my name is Pilanthorn.
I am a police officer.
My name is Sky. Sky means
the space above the Earth.
Huh?
The fourth corpse?
The deceased, Ms. Isriya Suphakorn, age 26 years.
The autopsy begins at 2:50 p.m.
The dead body is cold.
Flies have started to lay eggs.
The outer layer of skin begins to peel off.
Some blisters are starting
to dry up and some are still liquefied.
There are red and blue marks along the veins on the skin.
Muscle tone is decreased.
Are there any witnesses or relatives of the deceased who have filed a police report?
The deceased's father reported his daughter missing two weeks ago.
Oh my god!
My name is Sky. Sky means the space above the Earth.
Is Isriya here?
Oh, she's not here.
She hasn't come to work for several days now.
Is there something wrong?
Er...
Mom wanted Isriya to have this yarn.
But if Isriya isn't here, it's okay.
Sky will come again next time.
Alright, Miss.
What's up?
Huh?
The fourth corpse?
Yes, if you count the time the body was found,
but if consider the condition of the corpse,
this is the third body.
The kid was right, Lan.
Got it. Got it.
I'll be there.
An.
So the latest corpse...
died before the convenience store cashier?
Absolutely.
-Where did she die?
-In the abandoned building.
At first, I hadn't found the yarn,
so I haven't called to tell you yet.
How did she die?
The victim was tied to a crowd control barrier.
The cause of death was air embolism.
- Air, what?
- Well, it's a blood vessel embolism.
-Air is blocking the blood vessels. Can air kill people?
-Of course, it can.
Injecting more than two hundred milliliters
of air into a person.
It may cause airlock in the right ventricle.
There is an obstruction in the circulatory system.
It causes the right ventricle to stop working suddenly
and lead to Ischemic heart condition.
Does that mean the murderer is a doctor?
I'm not sure about this.
As far as I am concerned, the murderer knows Anatomy,
Physiology, and Pathology.
This is the yarn.
It was very bizarre.
Give me some paper and medical gloves.
-Lan, what are you going to do?
-Decode it.
-Huh?
-Decode this yarn.
Wait... Do you remember the previous riddle?
I don't.
That means we have to decode it from scratch.
Through Morse, right?
Yeah.
At first, we didn't think it was true.
Then let me help.
You write down the code.
Let's see how much I can decode.
How many dots are there?
Morse code.
Let's get started.
Dash, dash, dot, dash.
Dot, dot, dash.
"Dot, dot, dash."
No, no, let's start it all over. There's a gap.
Let's start it all over. I have to pause.
-Write down the next signal after I pause.
-Okay.
Dash, dash, dot, dash.
- Uh-huh.
- Dot, dot.
-Dash, dash, dot, dash.
-Uh-huh.
"Dash, dash, dot, dash."
-It's not working, there must be a space, sorry.
-Okay.
- Okay.
- There must be a space.
Dash, dot, dot.
Uh-huh. "Dash, dot, dot."
There's no more to it.
Dash, dot, dot, dash-- Wait.
- Okay, that's okay.
- No, no.
Let's start it all over.
Dot...
dash, dash, dash...
Dash, dash, dot, dash, dot, dash, dash, dot.
Dash, dot, dot, dash-- Wait.
Dash, dot, dot, dot.
- Okay, "Dash, dot, dot, dot."?
- Dash, dot, dot, dot. Dash, dot, dot, dot.
-Dash, dot, dot.
-Uh-huh. "Dash, dot, dot."
Dot...
- Dash, dot, dot, dot.
- Dash, dot, dot, dot."
-Yeah, dash, dot, dot, dot.
-Okay.
And then dot, dash, dash, dot.
Inspector.
What's up, Mark?
Why are you here?
And why she...?
Sis!
She just fell asleep. Let her sleep.
Er...
What are you doing, Inspector?
Why is the room so messy?
We are decoding the yarn.
Like...
what that autistic teen did?
Yeah.
Can I help you?
It's okay, it's almost done.
Okay.
Er... er, have you heard the news that they have put a curfew on people with murder genes?
Curfew?
The government has announced that people who
have murder genes must return home by 7:00 p.m.
Or they must take a witness with them.
Please keep the documents and evidence for me.
And please take care of her.
And where are you going?
Did you tell the government to declare a curfew?
I did not.
They just called to consult me.
I just gave some advice.
And you?
How is your work progressing
The culprit left a riddle at the crime scene.
What exactly is the message they are trying to give?
And to whom?
They're having fun killing people.
Intentionally mocking the authorities.
Mocking the law.
Murder genes.
Arrest them as soon as possible.
You know right?
That it would have a positive effect on my popularity.
I know.
It's time to get back to work.
And if there is any progress
just call me directly, no need to go through Pitak.
Understood.
Do you remember?
How much do I expect from you?
I never forget.
Why don't you go to school?
I don't want to be questioned by reporters.
I don't want to be scolded by my friends about you passing the Murder Genes law.
I did everything for the right thing.
I did it for the country.
We did good, so why should we be afraid?
You should be more proud of your father.
But you chose to believe the words of those idiots.
Dad, are you sure that you are doing this for the country
not doing it for myself?
You say that one more time.
I won't keep you, do you understand, Pilantorn?
I will hit you once more, and it will be the last time.
To remind you that you are my only child.
And to warn you
how much
your father expects from you.
Don't let me down, son.
Ouch!
In short, everything Sky said is true.
The binary code is the sequence of the victims.
Including the number of victims
that the murderer will kill, which is ten.
What about Morse code?
What is it? I'm totally confused.
Here.
Victim One
The murderer left a riddle:
"Count money every day, why am I not rich?"
It matches Victim Two, the bank employee.
Right.
And the riddle of the Victim Two was
"Welcome. Answer me, who am I?"
At first, we hadn't found the Victim Three,
so it didn't make sense.
But when we found the body, it was bingo.
The receptionist in the mall.
Victim Four...
"Popping up like mushrooms, at the grocery war"
If we hadn't found Victim Four first,
I wouldn't have a clue that
she's a convenience store cashier.
That's difficult.
"Pop up like mushrooms."
It's because convenience stores have emerged so quickly
that local grocery stores can't survive.
That's it, Sergeant. To sum it up...
The riddle on the yarn
will tell the next victim's occupation.
Exactly.
So if we guess the riddle correctly,
we will know who is likely to be the next victim.
Goodness!
The murderer is mocking the police.
So what is the next riddle?
"Receive food offerings in the morning,
barefoot walking on the ground."
Do we know what occupation is this?
(chanting in Pali)
- Kindly accept...
- The meal offering
- from all the attendants.
- We here all wish
- for the benefit,
- and happiness,
-to happen to us all.
-Forever and ever.
-Sathu.
Alright, take turns to offer the meal.
There's no need to rush. Everyone gets merit.
Did you knit it yourself?
My daughter knitted it.
Knitted Beautifully.
May you prosper.
Hey.
Do you think that the Venerable Monk
does not have the appearance of the 60s.
Look at him.
There are no wrinkles on his face.
This is probably because he is a practitioner.
I heard that he practices very strictly.
He doesn't eat meat at all
and does Vipassana instead of sleeping.
Right.
This is why they say that
people with merit are worthy of respect.
These days, it's very rare.
I hear nothing but scandalous news about monks.
If this wasn't the monk I know,
I don't worship at all.
-I'm afraid I won't get any merit.
-Right.
Now, everyone.
Today is a big Buddhist holy day.
If you have time,
come walk around the temple with candles
for good luck in your life.
It is a merit.
We will be able to carry it with us in the next life.
Come, let's prepare to pour water to dedicate merit.
(chanting in Pali)
I wish you happiness and prosperity.
What's wrong, Sky?
Put your hands together, Sky.
Put your hands together nicely.
What's the matter, Sky?
What's wrong?
How can you concentrate with such
loud noise? It's annoying, annoying.
Put your hands together, Sky.
It's okay, Sky.
Sky.
Here, Sky, the sound is gone. Come on, Sky, put your hands together nicely. The sound is gone.
Come on.
Sky, Sky, Sky, what's wrong with you, Sky?
I just saw him doing fine.
How could someone do something like this?
They're taking him out.
Who could do such a thing?
Right now, the police are
initially assuming that this may be
The same serial killer that the police are hunting down.
Because the murderer left behind a sheet of knitted yarn
just like in the previous incidents.
If this is true, this will be the fifth body in this case.
Now, people are very afraid.
Because the police themselves
were unable to catch the culprit.
Social trends are asking government officials
How many more deaths will have to occur before the criminals are caught.
And how will the people live?
Phra Phongsak Phonpanyawat, 64 years old
The autopsy begins at 10:10 a.m.
Hold on.
What
Are you going to do the autopsy yourself?
Why?
Well, you're a woman.
So what?
As a woman, how can you touch a monk?
You'll go to hell. I'm worried about you.
This is a corpse, not a monk.
Fine.
Such a sin.
Do whatever you have to do.
If it's a sin, then I'm the only one who sins.
Take a photo.
Arms are full of needle marks.
There are scars on the face.
Take a photo here.
Underneath the facial skin is not smooth.
It feels like there is something under the skin.
What is it, sis?
The skin has a wavy texture.
There are wavy marks under the skin.
How is it?
So you did the autopsy yourself?
Yes, she did it herself, Inspector.
I told her not to, but she wouldn't listen.
You'll get internet backlash for breaking the rules of monks.
Actually, the Venerable Monk had broken the rules way before that already.
Preliminary autopsy results.
Just look at it yourself.
We cannot call him a monk anymore.
The face was cut open
and the dermal filler came out like jelly.
Look at the X-ray film.
What is this?
A facelift thread.
That's why the Venerable
Monk has an aura of a face full of merit.
It's not because of any merit or virtue.
Glutathione.
This Venerable Monk?
Better say Venerable Nun.
- Wait... Wait a minute, An. What is this?
- Inspector, sir.
I found something in the monk's hut.
(3 hours ago)
What is it?
Why did the monk keep these things?
I think he's saving it for his mother.
-Hurry up and get it unlocked.
-Understood.
This is what's in the phone.
-What?
The third crown for Miss Tiffany is coming.
You see, she was really a nun as I said.
It doesn't end there.
I have questioned the temple boys.
The temple boys said that...
- Hello.
- Come in.
What should we do this time?
Give me everything, Bossy!
It's almost the big Buddhist holy day.
I have to meet the fans
and many disciples.
If my skin is not radiant and flawless,
People will gossip that I don't have enough merit.
Then I'll prepare the gluta
for you and give you a full dose.
And then add a vitamin drip.
I guarantee that the aura will be so bright like...
a glitter.
It's awesome.
Give it to me. Give me everything.
Come on. Now, I am very ready.
Come on! Come on!
Okay, let's go.
I'll add some dermal filler for orange cheeks.
And a little bit under the eyes
and a little bit on the laugh lines.
I assure you that your face
will definitely have a dimension of merit.
Great. May the merit from this time
bring prosperity to Bossy.
Have radiant skin like mine.
Come on, Bossy.
Got it, then it matches the cause of death.
She died because of the dermal
filler used for cosmetic injections.
Dermal filler?
The murderer injected a large amount of filler into the bridge of his nose.
Until it blocked the blood vessels
in the brain, causing death.
This is psycho.
Then the number one suspect right now
must be that quack doctor.
Right!
The suspect has medical knowledge.
There is a picture of that doctor on the monk's phone.
The temple boy confirmed
that this was a quack doctor named Boss.
- Investigate about him.
- Understood.
Sir.
What's up, Sergeant?
The profile of the quack doctor.
He has murder genes.
- Go, Sergeant.
- Right.
Police have now found clues to the serial killer
With a new report confirming
that the suspect has murder genes.
What are you watching, Sky?
Let me watch it.
- Sky will watch.
- What are you watching?
There are only stressful things. No more.
- Don't watch it, Sky.
- Please give me the remote. Sky will watch.
Do you know the people in this picture?
Is there something wrong?
Miss Sookwan.
Do you know this person?
This is a picture of Boss.
Boss is the person who rents our house.
Sky, sit here. I will go talk to the police.
Boss has been renting my house for many years.
But I don't know much about him.
When he pays the rent, he pays through an app.
We don't meet often.
Is there something wrong?
Now, Boss is the suspect in a serial murder case.
Ouch!
Open the door!
This is the police.
Hey, stop!
Boss, I told you to stop.
- Follow him.
- Okay.
Hey!
Fuck!
- Sergeant, call an ambulance right away.
- Okay.
The press conference said that the serial killer was dead.
I think we can't conclude that yet, sir.
What?
Why? You wrote the report yourself.
Indeed, Boss is related to Phra Phongsak.
But he is just a suspect.
Because we still don't have any evidence to confirm that Boss is the murderer.
In the previous cases,
there was no connection or motive at all.
The murder genes are the connection point.
Your father told us that these people
can kill without any reason at all.
But we need proof, don't we, sir?
The officer at Boss's house has already reported back
that no yarn has been found
or even a single piece of knitting equipment.
What kind of murderer
would leave evidence in their own room?
Sir,
I would like to confirm that
we still cannot close this case.
But I ordered it to be closed. That's it.
You can go out now.
What are you doing standing there?
Yes, sir.
What's up, An?
Okay, I'll be there.
Boss's hands are soft and smooth,
without even a single scratch.
Normally, people who knit will have marks on their fingers.
The more the criminal knits that much yarn,
the more skilled he must be.
It means that you have done a lot of work.
Hands can't be so spotless.
An is trying to tell me that...
It's just an assumption.
Did Boss have someone else knit it for him?
But I don't believe that.
Why did he have to run away
from the police if he wasn't a bad guy?
He's not a murderer.
But he is guilty of charges.
First, he is a quack doctor.
Second, he is a person with murder genes
who was outside during curfew.
The punishment is already severe for the second charge.
Why don't you look surprised?
I don't think that Boss is the real murderer either.
Hey!
If Boss wasn't a murderer,
this means there must be more victims, Inspector.
Who could possibly be?
The riddle on the yarn, have you decoded it yet?
What's the riddle, Inspector?
I've tried but I have no clue.
Because this riddle is not Morse code like every other time.
What?
So what should we do?
I would like to ask Sky to decode it for me once more.
What else do you want to decode? You said you had already caught the culprit.
Well, it's like this, Ms. Sookwan.
I want to prove something.
It won't take long.
I just want Sky to help me check it out.
Is there a code or just some letters on the sheet?
Sky isn't coming today.
Mom, Sky's here. Sky's here. Sky's here...
You said Sky wouldn't come.
I would. Sky comes to help mother
every day from 12 to 7.
Sky comes every day.
If you have any questions,
ask her quickly so you guys can leave.
It's like this, Sky.
I have a code and I'd like Sky to help me look at it.
What does it mean? Excuse me.
Braille.
It is a form of written language for blind people.
Invented by Louis Braille, a French blind teacher.
Braille is derived from his last name.
It has the appearance of small raised dots.
In one cell there are six dots.
They are arranged alternately to form a code instead of letters.
Right.
-What does it say, Sky?
-Morons...
Huh?
Morons need help from a retard kid.
Hey, are you really insulting the police inspector?
Hey, didn't you ask Sky what the culprit said?
And Sky already said it.
What did they say, Sky?
Morons need help from a retard kid.
Yeah, yeah, I know. No need to keep repeating it.
Sis.
She didn't mean to insult us, right?
The autistic children don't lie.
And is there anything else, Sky?
Any more hints?
5/10, not coffee with cher, who am I?
"Not coffee with cher, who am I?"
- Teacher?
I hope that you all come here for the last time.
But Miss Sookwan.
If the dead culprit was not the real murderer,
we could all be victims,
including you and your daughter.
And what was that press conference you were holding?
Are you fooling the people?
If that's the case,
you guys shouldn't come back here again.
Because it will cause trouble for me and my child.
She's so mean.
She's worried about her daughter.
Parents who have children like this
probably don't want their children
to get involved with a lot of people.
She was afraid that something might happen
and trigger the child's symptoms.
But at least we now know that
the next victim is likely to be a teacher.
Then what will you do?
Lan, what's with him? Why doesn't he talk to me?
Ouch!
Hey!
I have already announced the closing of the Yarn Murder case.
Are you going to continue?
Do you dare to disobey your superior's orders?
Between losing face and having more people die.
What would you choose?
I will not lose face.
And I won't let anyone else die.
Do whatever you want, but you have to know...
that if this case does not end,
the one who lost face is your father.
I will monitor every school as much as I can.
Just be careful.
Don't let it slip through the ears of reporters.
I don't want people to panic.
Does that mean you believe me?
But you can leave now. I don't want to complain to you.
Here is all the information that you ordered, both about Sookwan and her daughter.
Including all the victims, how many children, how many wives, how many secret lovers
Weight, height, medical history, birthplace.
What school did they attend,
what was their GPA, I give you everything.
Thanks, Sergeant. I'll read the rest myself.
Alright.
Oh, Inspector.
I have something to tell you.
Miss Sookwan used to be an operating room nurse.
Yes, knitting is about inserting a stitch into a loop.
Then pull the yarn to the end and slowly pull the yarn out.
When we do the purl stitch.
We have to pull the yarn forward
and then insert it upwards.
Wrap the yarn, pull out the yarn
and this is the purl stitch.
But if there is a pattern,
It depends on how the stick
is inserted up and down or how the yarn is wrapped.
And it will make patterns.
It's similar to tying a knot with a yarn.
It's also a way to create a pattern.
Do you understand?
Let's try it.
Are you starting the knit?
Ah, let's try it. I will check on each table.
Let's see if you can do it.
Hmm, is this one knitted?
Thank you very much, Ms. Sookwan,
for being a special teacher for our school.
My pleasure.
I am delighted that you have agreed
to be my special speaker today.
Thank you for not dwelling on the past.
Let bygones be bygones.
Agreed.
But before I can get through it,
it's quite difficult, Miss.
But don't worry.
I've forgotten all about it.
Thank you again.
Next time...
Please bring Sky along.
Sky probably doesn't want to come.
I must leave now.
Sorry, darling, there was a lot of traffic.
Before I arrive,
whom were you talking to?
Miss Sookwan.
She came to help as a special teacher
teaching Handicrafts.
Miss Sookwan is very good at knitting.
Let's go.
-Hello.
Is Isriya here?
Oh, she's not here.
She hasn't come to work for several days now.
Is there something wrong?
This is the yarn that Ya ordered.
I collected it and gave it to you.
I'm sorry for your loss.
- Thank you very much.
- We'd better get going.
This is what the shop owner came to give me.
Was Mr. Isriya close to the owner of the shop?
She liked knitting.
When she had free time, she knitted for people around her.
I also found out about this from her friends.
They said that she often went to buy things at this store.
I'm sorry to ask.
Did the shop owner say anything about your daughter?
She came to give her condolences
and gave me the yarn that Ya ordered.
Thank you very much.
These two people
studied at Arunpanya School.
Sky also studied here.
- It's an incredible coincidence.
- Such a suspicious coincidence.
And the digger we deep,
the more everything is connected
to Sky and Sookwan.
The victims died of medical techniques.
Miss Sookwan used to be a nurse.
Each victim had a sheet of yarn with a riddle.
Sky is the only one who can understand.
Two of the five victims knew the mother and daughter.
Sergeant, I'd like you to go ask Rapee if...
-she knows Miss Sookwan.
-Wow!
No need at all.
Yesterday I saw Miss Sookwan talking with my wife at school.
I remember Rapee said that
Miss Sookwan is a special teacher there.
Sky, where are you going in such a hurry?
Sky, come help me carry the stuff first.
Sky.
What are you doing here?
What's wrong with you?
Sky, why do you act so weird, sweetheart?
Sky.
I know she deserves this.